<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Scribe</string>
  <string name="app_description">The abstract game Scribe, designed by Mark Steere</string>

  <string name="red">Red</string>
  <string name="blue">Blue</string>
  <string name="empty">{empty}</string>

  <string name="msg_illegal_move">You cannot play in that mini-grid at this time</string>
  <string name="current_player">Current Player: </string>
  <string name="msg_confirm_new_game">Are you sure you want to start a new game? 
   The current game will be lost.</string>
  <string name="msg_confirm_exit">Are you sure you want to exit Scribe?</string>
  <string name="exit_scribe">Exit Scribe</string>
  <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
  <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
  <string name="glyphs">Glyphs</string>
  <string name="rules">Rules</string>
  <string name="about">About</string>
  <string name="market">Rate/Comment</string>
  <string name="back">Back</string>

  <string name="its_your_turn">It\'s your turn!</string>
  <string name="its_not_your_turn">Wait for opponent</string>
  <string name="wins_mini_grid">wins the mini grid!</string>
  <string name="wins">wins! Play again?</string>
  <string name="about_dialog_text">
    Game Design: <a href="http://www.marksteeregames.com">Mark Steere</a>\n\n
    Android app by: <a href="http://github.com/MatrixFrog">Tyler Breisacher</a>\n\n
    Heavily inspired by: <a href="http://superdupergames.org">Super Duper Games</a> 
  </string>

<string name="gameMode">gameMode</string>  
<string-array name="gameModeEntries">
  <item>Majority</item>
  <item>Super Glyph</item>
</string-array>
<string-array name="gameModeEntryValues">
  <item>majority</item>
  <item>superglyph</item>
</string-array>
<string name="majoritySummary">Majority: Whoever wins the majority of the nine mini grids wins overall.</string>
<string name="superglyphSummary">Super Glyph: Players form super glyphs on the super grid with their winning mini grids.</string>
<string name="defaultGameMode">Majority</string>
<string name="defaultGameModeValue">majority</string>

<string name="rules_intro">
 Scribe is a pen and paper game for two players. Nine mini grids together form 
 one super grid. Draws cannot occur in Scribe. Mark Steere invented
 Scribe on October 1, 2006.
</string>
<string name="rules_basicmoves">The two players take turns marking squares, one 
square per turn, until the entire super grid is filled. Players are not allowed 
to pass on their turn. On your first turn, you can claim any square on the super 
grid. The mini grid of your last move is treated as a map. The square you last 
claimed (marked with a small white dot) points to the mini grid in which you must 
make your next move. For example, in this screenshot, Red\'s last move was in the 
upper-right corner of a mini grid, so Red must now play in the upper-right mini 
grid, which is the only one that is not grayed out. If your last move points to 
a completely filled mini grid, you can make your next move anywhere in the super 
grid.</string>
<string name="rules_object">Press \"menu\" to see the 19 glyphs of Scribe. Each 
glyph is worth the number of dots that compose it. For example the J is worth 
six points. A glyph also represents its own mirror image and rotations. Glyphs 
appearing as a subset of a larger group don\'t count. When a mini grid is 
completely filled, the glyph points are tallied and the high score wins. 

\n\nMajority Version: Whoever wins the majority of the nine mini grids wins overall.
\n\nSuperglyph Version: Players form super glyphs on the super grid with their 
winning mini grids.</string>
<string name="rules_copyright">Original rules copyright \u00a9 by Mark Steere, 
October 2006. Modified slightly for the Android version.</string>
</resources>
